《闪电侠》前情回顾
Previously on "The Flash."
我现在宣布你们结为夫妇
I now pronounce you husband and wife.
我想你是时候给你那位恶毒的室友
I think it's time you introduced these guys
介绍一下这些人了
to your mean roommate.
告诉阿姆内特我要退出
Tell Amunet I'm out.
没人能逃出我的掌心  冰霜杀手
Nobody walks away from me, Frost.
那你是觉得迪沃和他妻子是超级大坏蛋
So you think that DeVoe and his wife are supervillains?
你到底是谁
who are you really?
我和你诞生于同一天晚上
I was born on the same evening you were.
我知道所有能想到的问题的答案
I know every answer to every question ever asked.
太不可思议了
Incredible!
克利福德
Clifford!
你的身体退化太快
Your body's deteriorating
椅子会承受不住
faster than the chair can handle.
会撑过去的
It will survive long enough.
你在干嘛
What are you doing?
用金属箔装饰
Tinsel.
你金属箔与树表面的比例太差了
Your tinsel to surface ratio is terrible.
-你开玩笑呢吧  -我很认真
- Are you kidding me? - I'm not kidding you.
我做了大量的研究
I've done extensive research
来确保这些金属箔
to make sure that this tinsel
跟这棵树的比例完美匹配
is properly proportioned for the tree.
-太差了  -差吗
- It's terrible. - It's terrible?
-我告诉你什么是差  -什么
- I'll tell you what's terrible. - What?
你这个圣诞怪杰太吝啬了
Your Scrooge to Grinch ratio is terrible.
你是个坏人
You're a mean one.
我不会用39.5寸的杆碰你的
I wouldn't touch you with a 39 1/2-foot pole.
没听说过
Haven't heard that one before.
对
Yeah.
西斯科  吉普赛在哪
Hey, Cisco, where's Gypsy?
她得加班
She had to work the holiday shift.
不过我给她准备了很好的礼物
But I think I got her the perfect gift.
一个古拉格级的机械刀
A Gulag-class mech knife forged in the unholy
由地球22上邪恶的血火制成  制造者是
blood fires of Earth-22 by none other than--
韦斯特2.0
West 2.0.
吉普赛现在应该给我发点什么了
Of course, Gypsy should have sent something for me by now.
尴尬  肯定没事的
Awkward. I'm sure it's fine.
呀  红鼻子驯鹿是不是
Yikes. Did Rudolph just
-在你的树上方便了  -好吧  好吧
- diarrhea all over your tree? - Cool, cool.
两个骗子  简直是个奇迹了
Two humbugs. It's a Festivus miracle.
别理解错了  拉尔夫喜欢圣诞节
No, don't get me wrong. Ralphie loves Christmas.
我每个节日都会给我奶奶打电话
I ring in every holiday season with my nana.
可她记不住我
She never remembers me,
不过我也这样
but I am getting that inheritance.
-你太不正常了  -如果你不想
- You are just incorrect. - Well, if you don't want
在圣诞节骗你祖母的话
to spend Christmas conning your grandma,
你可以去参加韦斯特家的派对
you're more than welcome to join your friends
很多朋友在那
at the West family party.
很明显  我知道的
Extremely obvious. I saw that.
顺便说一下  那个派对肯定很无聊
And by the way, that sounds like a snoozefest.
当然了  除非那里有小苏打
Unless, of course, you're serving baking soda.
小苏打
Baking soda!
啥  不好意思  那是什么
Wha-- sorry, what's that about?
这个  不能外传
Well, it's a... bit of an inside joke
是关于冰霜杀手的
actually concerning Killer Frost.
经典的冰霜杀手
Classic Killer Frost.
你们跟冰霜杀手一起玩吗
You guys were hanging out with Killer Frost?
-是的  -是的
- Oh, yeah. - Oh, yeah.
是的
Yeah.
-祝你们玩得高兴  -我们玩得可高兴了
- I hope you had a great time. - Oh, we had the best time.
我是说  你很好  冰锥
I mean, you're great, Snowcone.
不过我的女人更好
But my girl Frostbite, ai yi yi.
行了
Come on.
我去喝杯咖啡
I'm gonna go get a cup of coffee.
凯特琳
Caitlin!
如果你看到冰霜杀手
Hey, if you see my girl K-Frost later,
别忘了告诉她我说的小苏打的事
tell her what I said about the baking soda!
德比
Dibny!
过分了吗
Too much?
闪 电 侠
第四季
第九集
这是奥利弗和费利西蒂送的
Okay, from Oliver and Felicity.
我们有浓缩咖啡机了
We have an espresso machine. All right.
好吧  没有注册
Okay. Not on the registry,
不过我想在我们的婚礼期间结婚
but I guess getting married during our wedding
也没有注册  所以  好吧
wasn't on the registry, either. So, yeah, sure.
-我不是抱怨  -我把这个
- I'm not bitter. - I'll put this
放到回礼堆里面
in the return pile.
好了  看来都处理完了
Well, I guess that's everything.
不  还有一个  没有卡片
No, we got one more. There's no card.
真好  又是一套刀具
Great. It's another set of knives.
还不全  只有一把
It's not even a full set. Yeah, it's one knife.
-这也太劣质了吧  -给我看看
- That's just shoddy gifting. - Let me see.
我清理一下
I'm gonna clean up.
怎么  不用你的速度了吗
So, what, so no speed cleaning today?
不用  又没有急事
No, we're not in a rush.
巴里  你在巴厘岛也没怎么用超能力
Barry, you barely used your powers in Bali, either.
甚至抹防晒霜的时候也没有
I mean, not even to put on suntan lotion.
-那个是要喷的  -怎么了  巴里
- It was a spray-on bottle. - What is going on, Bar?
没什么
Nothing.
我也不知道  我最近一直在想
I mean, I don't know. I have been thinking recently
你知道的  我刚有超能力的时候
that, you know, when I first got my powers,
总是想去使用
I would use any excuse to use them.
在马路上飞驰
It would just be me and the road,
所有周围的一切都消失了
and everything around me would disappear.
我人生中第一次感觉到
It's like the first time in my life
我的内心平静了
I really felt like I was at peace.
现在我总是有这种感觉了
I just feel like that all the time now.
跟你在一起的时候不需要快
I don't have to run when I'm with you.
说得真好
That's so sweet.
我爱你  爱瑞丝·韦斯特·艾伦
I love you, Iris West Allen.
我也爱你
I love you, too.
我来吧
Let me.
我精细运动的技能萎缩得越来越快
The atrophy of my fine motor skills is accelerating.
很遗憾  亲爱的
I'm so sorry, my love.
痛苦稍纵即逝
Oh, the pain is but fleeting.
-今天是个大日子  -多好啊
- After all, today is the day. - How fitting.
你可以跟弥赛亚同一天生日
You'll share a birthday with the Messiah.
基督教徒直到春天才出生
The Nazarene wasn't born until spring.
你可以查一下星座规律来验证
You can check the constellation patterns to verify that.
这个知识你听过了  对吧
Oh, you've heard this lecture before, haven't you?
可能吧  但是你的声音
Maybe. But I will never grow tired
我永远听不够
of hearing your voice.
即使声音不是我的  但话还是我说的
The words are still mine. Even if the voice isn't.
-你有疑虑吗  -没有
- Do you have any doubts? - No.
当然没有
Of course not.
只是要适应一下
It will just take some getting used to.
别害怕  亲爱的
Don't be afraid, my love.
这是一项伟大的事业
This is the great work.
我发誓我很快就会回到你身边
I swear I will stand beside you in no time.
冬日冰霜杀手
摩卡星冰乐
咖啡是深度烘培还是浅度烘培呢
Well, it's the dark roast? The light roast?
你在喝的是顾影自怜烘培咖啡吗
What are you having, the self pity roast?
倒希望是
I wish.
-冰霜杀手摩卡星冰乐  -终于喝到了
- Oh, the Killer Frost. - Finally got a drink.
我非常开心她帮助大家打败了德意志军团
I'm thrilled that she helped everybody fight the Reichsmen,
但是我现在又摆脱不了她
but now it's like I can't escape her.
每个人不停地在说  冰霜杀手真有趣
Everybody keeps saying, "Killer Frost is so funny"
冰霜杀手真厉害  我一直都在担心
"Killer Frost is so badass" I spent so long worried
她会伤到人  但是现在
that she was gonna hurt people, but now,
大家却更愿意和我邪恶的一面
turns out people would rather hang out
一起玩
with my villainous alter ego.
我懂
Look, I-- I get it.
我知道有邪恶双重身是什么滋味
I know what it's like to have the evil doppelganger.
但你和我一点也不像
But you're not like me anyway.
不  你不一样  你很特别
No, you're different. You're... special.
你的朋友会更愿意和你一起玩
And your friends would much rather
而不是和她
be with you than with her.
-谢谢你  哈里  -不客气
- Thanks, Harry. - You're welcome.
简直就是一辈子的购买用品额度
This is, like, a lifetime supply of store credit.
罗里为什么会觉得我们需要吐司机
Why would Rory think that we needed 40 toasters?
他说有什么大减价销售
He said that there was some kind of fire sale.
-是他偷来的  -肯定他偷来的
- He stole them. - He definitely stole them.
没错
Yeah.
巴里
Barry!
-凯特琳  -是阿姆内特
- Caity! - That's Amunet.
躲起来  躲起来
Hide, hide, hide!
我把你的格洛克手枪给堵住了
I blocked your glock.
你好  爱瑞丝
Hello, Iris.
我对你们的婚礼致以最深切的祝贺
My deepest congratulations on your wedding.
别变  亲爱的
No, no, dear.
霜霜融掉了  我要找的是你  凯特琳
Frosty melted away. I've come for you, Caity.
-你没事吧  -没事
- You okay? - Yeah.
我马上就回来
I'll be right back.
巴里
Barry!
迪沃  他在街上攻击我们
DeVoe. He attacked us on the street.
-他把巴里带走了  -什么
- He took Barry. - What?
-你在说笑吗  -你出了什么事
- Are you kidding me? - What happened to you?
阿姆内特·布莱克把凯特琳掳走了
Amunet Black abducted Caitlin.
两个人同时失踪
Two people go missing at the same time.
太巧合了吧
That's quite a coinkie-dink.
观察得真好  明知故问
Yeah, that's a great observation, Captain Obvious.
你能不能设置卫星找找
Can you set the satellite to look
凯特琳超凝态过冷能量
for Caitlin's cryokinetic energy
或是巴里的神速力标志
or Barry's Speed Force signatures?
不不  我们两种都要找
No, no, we've gotta look for both of them.
西斯科  我要你用震波感应一下巴里
Cisco, I need you to vibe Barry.
我要知道他还活着
I need to know that he's alive.
真是见鬼了
Holy poltergeist!
你没事吧
Hey, are you okay?
没事  我只是短期内不能再使用震波了
Yeah, I'm just not gonna be vibing again for a while.
震波感应到艾伦了吗
What about Allen?
他所在的地方  我从来没有经历过
Wherever he is, I've never experienced anything like it.
有人吗
Hello?
我们到了
Here we are.
真是走在世界最前沿啊
Really moving up in the world.
多一点热情又不会死
You know, a sprinkle of enthusiasm would not kill you.
阿姆内特  不管你有什么计划
Listen, Amunet, whatever it is you have planned,
我向你保证冰霜杀手绝对不想参与
I guarantee you Killer Frost wants nothing to do with it.
没错  亲爱的  我不需要她
So right, darling. I don't need her.
我需要的是你
I need you.
来见见你的病人吧
Meet your patient.
你干了什么
What have you done?
没必要表现得这么夸张吧
Oh, there's no need to be over dramatic.
他没死
He's alive.
我相信只要镇静剂药力过去后
And I'm sure he'd be happy to meet you
他会很高兴见到你的
just as soon as that tranquilizer wears off.
你为什么抓他  抓他来干什么
Why do you have him? What is he to you?
会下金蛋的鹅
My golden goose.
多米尼克是一个讨人喜欢的新超能力者
You see, dominic here is a delightful new meta
是我"找到"他的
that I... found.
我本来打算卖掉他的
And I'd intended on selling him,
但是可惜  他不愿意乖乖地
but unfortunately he did not want to go so gently
睡觉  所以...
into the good night. And, um...
-我开枪打伤了他  -他
- I shot him. - Uh, he's...
急需医疗救治
In desperate need of medical attention.
我知道
I know.
现在你知道我为什么需要你了  凯特琳博士
And now you know why I need you, Caity, M.D.
你在说的是在最佳情况下
You're talking about an intricate cranial foreign body
复杂的颅骨异物收缩
retraction at best.
而最坏的情况是需要做内窥镜检查
At worst that's an endoscopic--
我要打断你的话
I'm gonna stop you there,
因为我完全不知道你在说什么
'cause I've absolutely no idea what you're saying.
但是你知道吗  这根本不重要
But you see, it does not matter,
因为我知道你会明白要做些什么
because I knew that you would understand what needed to happen.
阿姆内特  我不会也做不了
Amunet, I won't. I can't.
这里没有经过消毒
This environment isn't sterilized.
仪器太老旧
The equipment is ancient.
看来我可以自己把子弹挖出来
I suppose I could just yank it out myself.
然后让他的血流干
And risk him bleeding out,
或是产生一堆其他的大脑缺陷
or a dozen other brain deficits.
好吧  说得对
Right. Good point.
只有一个办法能知道
Well, there's only one way to find out.
不要
No, no.
我会尽力而为
I'll do what I can.
好极了
Excellent.
我差点忘了
Oh, I almost forgot.
他死了  你也活不成
Should he die, you die as well.
冰霜杀手摩卡星冰乐太好喝了
This Killer Frost iced mocha is really delicious.
你好  艾伦先生
Hello, Mr. Allen.
这里不是尖端科研实验室
Not exactly S.T.A.R. Labs.
-你是谁  -我叫凯特琳·斯诺
- Who are you? - My name is Caitlin Snow,
你现在在圣安德鲁斯医院
and you're in St. Andrew's Hospital.
至少我觉得我们是
At least, I think that's where we are.
这个地方已经关闭了有一段时间
This place has been closed down for a while.
求你一定要帮我逃出去
Please, you have to help me get outta here.
-说得容易做起来难  -那个金发女士呢
- Easier say than done. - That blonde lady?
她也把你抓来了吗
She took you, too?
天呐  我不知道我们为什么会发生这种事
God, I don't understand why this is happening to us.
多米尼克  你知道什么是超能力者吗
Dominic, do you know what a meta human is?
听着  我没做错事
Listen, I-- I didn't do anything wrong.
我没抢劫银行  没干坏事
I didn't rob a bank or something.
是  我知道  有超能力的人
No, I know. People with abilities--
像你这样的人  他们都是有用的东西
people like you-- they're a commodity.
-尤其是  -尤其是对阿姆内特来说
- Especially-- - Especially to Amunet.
没错
Yeah.
我要和你说实话
Listen, I'm gonna be honest with you.
要治好她给你所带来的伤害不容易
It would be very difficult to fix what she did to you,
即使是在有合适仪器的最好环境下
even under the best of circumstances with the right equipment.
但我感觉没事  我的脑袋都不疼
But I feel fine. My head doesn't even hurt.
这是一个小奇迹  但如果那个碎片
Which is a minor miracle. But if that shard
-损坏了的话  -会导致永久性
- were to fracture- - It could cause permanent
运动技巧与并行大脑损伤
motor skills and parallel brain deficits.
你是怎么...
How did you...
你有心灵感应能力
You have telepathic abilities.
你能听到我现在思考的内容吗
Can you hear what I'm thinking right now?
我们什么时候获得的能力
When did I get my powers?
几个月前
A couple months ago.
我坐公交车去机场上班
I took the bus to my job at the airport.
安检人员  但是我到那里之后
TSA. But when I got there,
所有人就好像在疯狂的冲我喊叫
it was like everyone was yelling at me screaming mad.
但是他们的嘴没有动
But their mouths weren't moving.
只有在我离某人很近的时候才行
It only works when I'm close enough to see someone.
你觉得咱们没法出去了吗
You don't think we're getting out of here?
我会尽一切努力拯救你
I'm gonna do everything I can to fix you,
但是我不能带你离开她身边
but I can't get you away from her.
我自己不行
Not on my own.
凯瑟琳  我也害怕
Caitlin. I'm scared, too.
不错的亮相
What an entrance.
咱们在哪  这是你的避难所吗
So, where are we? This is your sanctuary?
你是怎么看出来的
What gave that away?
迪沃  如果你想杀了我
DeVoe, if you wanted to kill me,
你把我电死在大街上就行了
you could have just electrocuted me on the street.
-我在这是有原因的  -是的  艾伦先生
- So I'm here for a reason. - Yes, Mr. Allen.
这样我就可以教导你了  毕竟
So that I may teach you. I am, after all,
我始终是个教师
first and foremost, a teacher.
天啊
Oh, God.
好吧  行
All right. Fine.
教我吧  但是首先让我确认下
Teach me. But first I wanna make sure
看我学得怎么样  你先派机士来找我
I'm all caught up. You sent your Samuroid after me.
你计划将我从
You arranged to pull me
神速力中拖了出来
out of the Speed Force.
你确保我将巴士上那群人都变成
You made sure that we turned all those people on that bus
超能力者  为什么
into meta humans. Why?
你看  我行为上的细节
You see, the finer points of my agenda
不在今天的教学大纲中
is not part of today's syllabus.
别这样  咱可以插节课
Oh, come on. We can squeeze it in.
-我学得很快  -得了吧
- I'm a fast learner. - Please.
你那脑容量  能看懂我计谋
You're about as capable of seeing the breadth
之宏大的难度  就如同让婴儿
of my machinations as an infant
掌握多变量物理一样
mastering multivariable physics.
我今天为你准备的教程更加简单一些
The lesson I have prepped for today is much more simple.
生活第一守则
Life 101.
这世上没有快乐结局
There are no happy endings.
咱们有位客人
We have a guest.
-迪沃  -你应该学着
- DeVoe? - You should learn to lose
时不时的输一次  巴仔
every once in a while, Bar.
一次小耻辱能帮助你做好准备
A little humility will prepare you for what lies ahead.
现在  请允许我失陪了
Now, if you will excuse me.
迪沃
DeVoe!
如果你敢伤害他  你要是碰了他的话
If you hurt him-If you put a hand on him...
迪沃
DeVoe!
打开了
It's open.
晚上好  韦斯特警探
Good evening, detective West.
我感觉你不是为了我妻子
Something tells me you're not here for more of my wife's
-著名的柠檬汁来的  -我的儿子在哪
- world-famous lemonade. - Where's my son?
艾伦先生  他失踪了吗
Mr. Allen, has he gone missing?
他没有失踪  他被抓走了
He's not missing. He was taken.
被一个为迫不及待想会一会的人
By someone I am eager to meet.
先不提这明显的威胁  韦斯特先生
Thinly veiled threats aside, Mr. West,
恐怕我不知道巴里·艾伦的所在
I'm afraid I have not a clue as to Barry Allen's location.
但我却知道  你的同事就在
I do know, however, that your colleague is located
我前厅后边  拿着一把离子交叠
behind my front porch carrying an ionic sub-repeating
脉冲武器
pulse firearm.
鸟池那里的的位置非常有利
The bird bath has a much better vantage point.
聪明人会去那里守着
A smart man would have taken up position there.
更聪明的人会知道这把枪没有保险
A smarter man would understand that this gun has no safety,
并且我的手指还在扳机上
and my finger is still on the trigger.
有什么让你觉得好笑吗
Is there something you find funny?
我发现这里边有一个很有趣
Well, it has occurred to me that there is an amusing
很讽刺的事  你作为一个警探
irony at play. You being a detective and all,
却不知道在失踪儿童案件中
yet you fail to acknowledge the most basic result
-最常见的结果  -那是什么
- in missing children cases. - And what would that be?
也许是你的儿子离家出走了
Well, perhaps your son just ran away.
-别  -我可是有
- Don't. - Now, I do have
针对你儿子的限制令
a restraining order against your son.
要不要我把你也加进去
Shall I add you to the list?
如果巴里出了什么事
If something happened to Barry,
这地球上可没有什么限制令
there ain't a restraining order on Earth
能够阻挡我抓住你
that would keep me from getting you.
我会带着逮捕令回来
I'm coming back with a search warrant.
完全没有必要  警探
Completely unnecessary, Detective.
如果你想搜查我的住处
If you desire to search my abode,
请随意
by all means.
你没有你想的那么聪明
You're not as smart as you think.
我有
Yes, I am.
快啊
Come on!
你只是在伤害你自己
You're only hurting yourself.
超音速奔跑  振动穿墙
Running faster than sound, vibrating through walls,
甚至是投掷闪点
even throwing lightning.
都不能摧毁这个屏障
None of that can destroy this barrier.
你对我的能力挺了解的
You know a lot about my abilities.
这就是我在这里的原因吗
Is that why I'm here?
迪沃想要我的能力
DeVoe wants my powers?
你不需要这么做
You don't have to do this.
不管他计划了什么  你不需要帮助他
Whatever he has planned, you don't have to help him.
一个帮手  你是这么看我的吗
A helper? Is that what you think I am?
一个无脑的奴才听候主人的命令
A mindless minion carrying out her master's bidding?
-某种邪恶秘书吗  -你说呢
- Some sort of evil secretary? - You tell me.
不  艾伦先生
No, Mr. Allen.
我将永远是我丈夫的伙伴
I am now and forever will be my husband's partner.
我明白
I understand that.
你不是唯一一个发誓
You're not the only one who promised
不论顺境逆境都对爱人不离不弃的
to stand by your loved one for better or for worse.
还有无论健康或是疾病
In sickness and in health.
如果你追随迪沃走上这条路
If you go down this path with DeVoe,
你看不出这是冒着风险牺牲
can't you see that you risk sacrificing everything
你们的一切
that you have together?
-你们的婚姻吗  -你还没搞懂
- Your entire marriage? - You're missing the point.
我就是为了我的婚姻愿意牺牲一切
I am willing to sacrifice everything for my marriage.
我想问你会不会做同样的事
I'd ask if you could do the same,
但没有这个必要
but there's no need.
我丈夫已经知道答案了
My husband already knows.
他的身体或许是人类
His body may be human,
但是他的大脑比你们都聪明
but his brain is smarter than yours.
-吓死我了  -怎么了这是
- Sark me! - What happened?
卫星在试图搜索
Well, the satellite's trying to search
巴里的神速力能量
for Barry's Speed Force energy
以及凯瑟琳的冷冻能力信号
and Caitlin's cryokinetic signature,
所以带宽限制过热了
so the bandwidth limiters are overheating.
当你依靠于机器而非侦探大师时
Well, that's what you get when you rely on machines
就会出现这种情况
rather than a master private eye.
我处理过数不清的失踪人口案件
I've had a ton of missing person cases.
有一次是一个妻子
There was this wife once.
结果是她伪造了自己的死
Turns out she faked her own death.
她好端端地住在亚利桑那州
She was just living in Arizona.
你意思是巴里伪装了自己的死
Are you saying Barry faked his own death
搬去亚利桑那州了吗
and moved to Arizona?
-不是  -那快闭嘴吧
- Well...no. - Well, then shut up.
天呐
Oh, boy.
你查到了些什么吧
Tell me you got something.
一无所获
Got nothing.
把迪沃家翻了个底朝天
Searched the DeVoe house thoroughly.
什么都没  你父亲
It's clean. Your father's gone
去巴里被掳走的现场调查去了
to check the scene from where Barry was taken.
以前有这么一起案子
You know, there was this other case once.
一女的找不到她老公了
Woman couldn't find her husband.
后来才知道她是有健忘症
Turns out she just had amnesia.
她老公在家  她只是没认出来
He was home. She just didn't recognize him.
然而她还是付钱给我了  还付了两次呢
And I still got paid. Twice.
拉尔夫  拜托
Ralph. Please.
闭  嘴
Shut. Up.
你是有话和我说吗  拉蒙
You got something you wanna say to me, Ramon?
没错
Yeah.
我是有话和你说  臭小子
Yeah, I got something to say to you, Ralphie boy.
凯特琳被绑架了
Caitlin's been kidnapped.
当然  如果不是你今天表现得
Of course, she wouldn't have been at Jitters
和个混蛋一样  她一开始就不会去
in the first place if you hadn't acted
吉特斯咖啡厅  但当然了
like such a jackass today, but of course,
拉尔夫·德比就是这样  都是你这张破嘴
in true Ralph Dibny fashion, you drove her away
把她赶走了
with your fat mouth!
也许我一开始就该揍你一顿
Maybe I should have turned my hand into a fat fist.
-别别  -是吗
- Hey, hey, hey! - Oh, yeah?
冷静
Guys, cool it.
我们爱的人身陷危险
Listen, the people we love are in danger,
而你们还不团结起来吗
and you can't get it together?
真要这样吗
Really?
随你
Whatever.
我去我的实验室想办法
I'll be in my lab.
我会去离他最远的房间
And I will be in whatever room is farthest from that.
极速实验室
Speed lab.
-谢谢  -不客气
- Thank you. - You're welcome.
这两人是怎么了
What is wrong with those two?
你
You.
什么
Excuse me?
你知道怎么了
You know what's wrong.
你是队长
You're the team leader.
队长应该做出最艰难的决定
Team leader's supposed to make the tough call.
我做了
I made a call.
我说了应该把两个人都找回来
I said we would look for both of them.
不  那不是选择
No. Looking for both of them is not a choice.
我们让自己的资源  成员压力过大
We're overtaxing our resources, our people,
因为你没有面对严峻的事实
because you won't face the hard truth.
事实是  不可能两个人都去找
And the hard truth is, we can't look for both.
只能找一个
We can only look for one.
哈里
Harry,
我刚许下守护巴里的誓言
I just made a vow to love and protect Barry.
对他坚贞不渝
To stand by him through thick and thin.
现在你让我在老公的生命
And now you're asking me to choose
与朋友中做出选择
between my husband's life and my friend's?
我做不到
I can't. I--I can't do that.
你必须得这样
You have to.
不然两个人我们都可能失去
Or we risk losing them both.
你必须要选择
You have to choose.
该死
Damn it.
谁是冰霜杀手
Who's Killer Frost?
抱歉  我一直想到她
Sorry, she's just on your mind a lot.
伴随着很多诅咒
With a lot of cursing.
她是我的超能力
She is my meta power.
我害怕或生气时  她就现身了
Whenever I get scared or angry, she takes over.
她暴力  危险  不可预知
She is violent and dangerous and unpredictable,
但她比现在的我有用多了
but she's a whole lot more useful than I am.
别这么说
No, thanks.
我已经被一个疯女人吓得要死了
I'm already scared to death of one psychotic woman.
我还是把机会押你这儿吧
I'll take my chances with you.
多米尼克  抱歉
Dominic, I'm sorry.
在这里做手术  风险太大了
It's too risky to perform this surgery here.
我也没有超能力救彼此
And I don't have any powers to save us.
但你有
But you do.
右边
Take a right.
凯特琳  回来
Caitlin, get back.
有人淘气了
Somebody's made my naughty list.
先生们  带多米尼克进去
Gentlemen, can you please take Dominic in?
我得单独和凯特琳聊聊
I need to have a word with Caity in private.
谢谢
Thank you.
怎么不感激我对你的好呢
Why can't you just appreciate how nice I've been to you?
我觉得你不理解好的意思
I don't think you understand the meaning of the word nice.
现在不是斗嘴的时候
Now, now. It's not about words.
该用行动说话了  我一次都没有捅过你
It's about actions. And I have not stabbed you
也没有揍你  也没有朝你开枪
or punched you or shot a deadly piece of metal at you once.
今天
Today.
你为什么要跑
So why did you run away from me?
我试了  而且失败了
Tried. Tried and failed.
冰霜杀手应该能做到
Killer Frost would have been able to do it.
我明白了
I see.
知道我在成为你眼前这个成功的企业家之前
Caity, do you know what I was doing before I became
是做什么的吗
the successful entrepreneur you see before you today?
恶毒的英国保姆吗
Mean British nanny?
不
No.
我以前是个女服务生
I was a stewardess.
看  和你不同
You see, unlike you,
我没有很厉害的科学家父母
I did not have fancy scientists for parents.
我没有学术成就或在很棒的机构做事
I did not collect scholarships or attend fine institutions.
我的事业选择
My career options were...
很有限
limited.
我日复一日穿着奇怪的短裙
So I spent my days in a quaint little skirt
给手脚不干净的飞行员供应咖啡
in there serving coffee to handsy pilots,
却无力阻止他们
powerless to stop them.
但粒子加速器爆炸了
But then the particle accelerator exploded.
我不再无力了
And I was powerless no more.
我用行动告诉那些飞行员们他们不该那么对我
I showed those pilots the error of their ways.
-和我说这些干嘛  -因为
- Why are you telling me this? - Because.
获得超能力塑造了现在的我
Obtaining my powers was quite literally what made me me.
但你这里却不是这情况
But the same cannot be said about you.
有很多医生
There are any number of doctors
我可以找来做这个手术
I could have come to for this procedure.
但我没有  我找了你
I did not. I came to you.
因为你  凯特琳·斯诺
Because you, Caitlin Snow,
你一直以来都是那么的出色
are and have always been remarkable.
你那么聪明  那么机智
You are bright, resourceful,
那么坚韧不屈
resilient.
我非常坚信你能做到
And I am more than certain you can do this.
好了  既然如此  除非你想把
So, with that said, unless you want to spend
剩下的医学生涯都浪费在这间停尸房
the rest of your medical career in the morgue,
我建议你振作起来  亲爱的
I suggest you buck up, darling.
穿上你的白大褂
You know, pull on your big girl pants
去做手术吧
and do the bloody thing.
找到凯特琳和巴里
Find Caitlin and Barry.
快点  你个笨蛋  快找啊
Come on, you bum! Do it!
找啊
Do it!
你在对我的卫星大吼大叫吗
Are you yelling at my satellite?
没  我只是在鼓励它
No, I was just encouraging it.
不过很明显  萨利不愿接受鼓励
Although Sally here clearly doesn't wanna be encouraged.
好吧  第一  她的名字不叫萨利
Okay. One, her name isn't Sally.
第二
Two...
对不起
I'm sorry.
巴里和凯特琳
Barry and Caitlin.
我们之前曾失去过他们俩
We've lost them both before,
现在就像是我们刚把他们找回来
and it just feels like we just got them back.
对不起  我之前那么混蛋
Well, sorry I was a dick.
你不是混蛋
You weren't a dick.
我才是混蛋  于公于私都是
I'm the dick. Private and public.
你只是不诚实罢了
You were just being unhonest.
如果不是因为我
If it wasn't for me,
凯特琳现在会和你  我  萨利在一起
Caitlin would be right here with you, me, and Sally.
-她不叫萨利  -老实说
- Not Sally. - The truth is,
好一段时间里  我都没有什么朋友
I...haven't had friends in a while.
你肯定觉得这很难以置信
I'm sure you find that hard to believe,
我长得那么标致  个性又那么讨喜
given my good looks and winning personality.
但我太久没练  都生疏了
But I'm out of practice.
我真是个特别糟的朋友
I suck at being a friend.
现在圣诞节毁了  大家都被绑架了
Now Christmas is ruined. Everyone is kidnapped.
全都是我的错
And it's all my fault.
你这不是来了
You're here.
在尽力帮忙
And you're helping.
凯特琳现在的状况很不妙
Caitlin's in a vulnerable state right now.
巴里可以照顾好自己
And Barry can take care of himself.
所以让我们关上神速力卫星
So let's turn off the Speed Force satellite.
去找凯特琳
We're going after Caitlin.
就这么定了
We're on it.
去找回凯瑟琳吧
Let's go get our girl.
我用了一些在地下室找到的设备
I used some equipment that I found in the basement
拼凑出一台核磁共振仪  以免伤到动脉
to jerry-rig an MRI machine so that I don't hit an artery.
真是心灵手巧
Now that's ingenuity. You know,
我就知道你是我们该绑架的医生
I knew you were the right doctor to kidnap.
这个手术的难度很高
This is a very delicate procedure.
你能给我点空间吗
Do you mind giving me some space?
没错  抱歉  我就...
Right, sorry. I'll just, um--
我就把这个放在这里
I'm gonna leave this right here.
你懂的  就是当做医疗保险之类的
You know, medical insurance and all.
很好
Great.
-准备好了吗  -我相信你
- Ready? - I trust you.
现在我要你身体别动
Now I need you to hold still.
你可能会感受到压力
You might feel some pressure.
正在取出异物
Extracting the foreign object.
异物已经取出
Foreign object extracted.
使用外科粘合剂
Applying some surgical glue.
-他进入休克了  -那就别让他休克
- He's going into shock. - So unshock him!
我不知道行不行
I don't know if I can.
稳定有节奏的心跳声
That is not the rhythmic tune
可不是这样的
of a steady heartbeat!
我要听到那种"哔  哔"声  亲爱的
I need to hear a "Beep, beep, beep," Dearie,
否则要在这躺尸的就不只是多米尼克了
or Dominic won't be the only flatliner in the room.
你可真行
You're good.
没问题了
We're clear.
他们都晕过去了吗
They're all out?
吸入40单位的吸入式麻醉剂吗
40 PSI of inhalation anesthetic?
足够把他们放倒  但挺不了多久
That'll keep them out, but not for long.
走吧
Let's go.
卫星正在定位
The satellite's pinging
凯特琳的潜在冷冻能力信号
Caitlin's latent cryokinetic signature.
她在哪
Where is she?
圣亚力山大医院东楼
East wing of St. Alexander Hospital.
那地方已经关了很多年了
That place has been closed for years.
我们马上就过去  战衣准备好了吗
We'll breach over. You got your suit?
外出必带
Never leave home without it.
凯瑟琳
Caitlin!
该死的  我瞄准的是你脑袋
Damn it! I was aiming for your head.
真是刺人
So pointy!
这样可不好  女士
That is not very nice, lady.
你是穿越来的吗
Are you a time traveler?
因为那身吓人的白人女行头
'Cause those white girl dreads
完全就是九十年代的好吧
came straight from the '90s.
虽然他那么说
Yeah, what he said.
但如果你想给我留个你的电话
Although, if you wanna give me your phone number,
我们还可以约一下  或者
we could Netflix and chill, or--
不可能
Impossible.
没错  就是这样
Well, that's the thing.
我就是不可能
I am the impossible.
我们打造那间牢房就是要让你无法逃脱
We built that cell so you couldn't run your way out.
我可没跑  我只是以很快的速度
I didn't run. Just stood still.
-站着不动  -你的振动频率比
- Really fast. - You vibrated faster
人眼能处理的频率还要快
than the eye can process.
就如你妻子所说的
Like your wife said,
你的大脑或许比我要聪明
your brain may be smarter than mine,
但你的身体还是人类的身体
but your body is still human.
都结束了  迪沃
It's over, DeVoe.
还早呢  艾伦先生
Far from it, Mr. Allen.
漂浮模式已激活
Flotation mode activated.
救生筏的确是个好主意  西斯科
Life raft was a good call, Cisco.
巴里
Barry!
-没有迪沃的踪影  -房子是空的
- There's no sign of DeVoe. - The house is empty.
人脸识别并没有查找出他或他的妻子
Facial recognition's not picking up him or his wife.
那又怎样  难道他就这么溺死了
So, what? He just drowned?
或是回到他囚禁巴里的什么地方了
Or went back to wherever he was holding Barry.
-你认为他为什么抓你  -我不知道
- Why do you think he took you? - I'm not sure.
但我想他对我的能力很有兴趣
But I think that he's interested in my powers.
电影《欢乐满人间》的主人翁仙女玛丽
真棒  我们的邪恶版玛丽阿姨
Great. We got evil Mary Poppins
也在收集超能力者
collecting metas, too.
没错  阿姆内特不会就此罢休的
Yeah, and Amunet won't back down.
没什么能比未解决的危急更能让人进入
Nothing like a lingering threat to put us all
-圣诞节气氛了  -说到这个
- in the Christmas spirit. - Speaking of which,
因为迪沃的事  还有塞西尔出城的事
with all this DeVoe stuff and Cecile being out of town,
我都没能有机会布置下房间
I didn't have a chance to decorate the house.
如果你们还想过圣诞节的话
If you guys still wanna do Christmas.
当然  我们有好多事情需要庆祝
Yeah, of course. We have a lot to celebrate.
你们介意我邀请多米尼克吗
Do you mind if I invite Dominic,
-我们救下的超能力者  -人越多越好
- that meta we just saved? - The more the merrier.
我们去准备酒水
Let's get some nog.
所有事情都解决了对吧
So everything worked out, huh?
是  但如果没能解决呢
Yeah, but what if it didn't?
如果因为我的决定  你被他杀了呢
What if he killed you because of a decision that I made?
老实说  巴里
Honestly, Barry,
我不知道自己能不能继续做下去
I don't know if I can keep doing this.
威尔斯已经跟我说了你昨天做的艰难决定
Wells told me about the tough call you had to make yesterday.
而你今后会做更多这样的决定
You're gonna have to make a lot more in the future.
但你的决定是对的
But you made the right call.
我为你做出决定感到骄傲
I'm proud of you for making it.
现在怎么办
So, what now?
现在我们去过个愉快的圣诞节
Now we have ourselves a merry little Christmas.
走吧
Let's go.
什么情况
What the...
等等
Oh, wait.
-像个装满果冻的碗  -拉尔夫  这怎么回事
- Like a bowl full of jelly. - Ralph, what is all this?
乔说他没时间装饰
Well, Joe said he didn't have any time to decorate,
而我想帮朋友排忧解难
and I wanted to do something nice for my friends.
我发现我的言行通常都不太合适
I realize that I don't usually say or do the right thing.
所以我想跟大家道歉
So I just wanted to say I'm sorry.
你真是下了一番工夫  拉尔夫  谢谢
Well, you--you really went all out, Ralph. Thanks.
很漂亮  谢谢你
Yeah, it looks great, man. Thank you.
很高兴你喜欢
Well, I'm glad you like it.
凯特琳
Caitlin.
我不应该说冰霜杀手
It was wrong of me to say that Killer Frost
比你好  因为事实是
is better than you. Because the truth is...
-谁都没你好  -谢谢
- no one is better than you. - Thank you.
这不用你说  因为这次是我拯救了危机
And, I know. I'm the one who saved the day this time.
西斯科  你有个礼物
You know, Cisco, a gift came for you
从你称为缺口的那种死亡破洞里出来的
through one of those death holes that you call a breach.
看来吉普赛来过了
Well. Looks like Gypsy came through, I guess.
等等
Wait.
这是分手盒子
This is a break up cube.
你和吉普赛处得不是挺好的吗
I thought things were going so well with you and Gypsy.
我也这么想的
That makes two of us.
拉蒙  这不是分手盒子
Ramon, that's not a break up cube.
你该等你一个人时打开
You should open that when you're alone.
不不  如果她要跟我分手
No, no, no, if she's gonna break up with me,
我想听听原因
I wanna hear why.
别  拉蒙  我就不会...好吧
No, Ramon, I wouldn't-- Okay.
西斯科  有人说
Cisco, somebody told me
今年你非常调皮
you've been a very naughty boy this year.
你不如来找我叮叮咚咚吧
Why don't you come over and jingle my bells, huh?
-苍天啊  -想找我叮叮咚咚吗
- Sweet baby Jesus. - Wanna jingle my bells?
都说了不是分手盒子
Told you, not a break up cube.
-我保证...  -按同一个按钮
- And I promise... - Use the same button to--
肯定会是闹腾的一晚
It's not gonna be a silent night.
-乔  介不介意  -拿回你家
- Joe, do you mind if I-- - Take that to your house.
好
Yeah.
沃利没来
No Wally?
他赶不过来
He couldn't make it.
他还在蓝谷吗
He still in Blue Valley?
在柬埔寨
Cambodia.
多米尼克  很高兴你来了
Dominic, I'm so glad you came.
进来吧  这是乔
Come on in. This is Joe.
谢谢
Thank you.
这房子...
This house is...
-很棒  -很喜庆
- Bitchin'? - Festive.
谢谢夸赞  但是
Thanks for the compliment, but, uh,
你是谁来着
who the hell are you again?
你刚刚帮忙救下的就是他
He's the guy you just helped save.
对  能读心的超能力者
Yeah, a meta who can read your mind.
很好  那他就知道
Good. Then he knows that I'm thinking
我在想团队只容得下一个新人
that there's only room for one new guy in this group,
也就是我
and that's me.
我不是来打击罪犯或取代号的
I'm not here to fight crime or get a code name.
是来头脑风暴搞清我的超能力的
Just to brainstorm ideas about my powers.
那我给你赐名"头脑风暴"
I hereby christen thee "Brainstorm."
拜托  我都来了几个月了
Oh, come on, man! I've been here for months,
还没有名字呢
and I don't have a name yet.
怎么  怎么了
What, what is it?
小阁楼的警报
Security at the loft.
估计又有礼物送来了
It's probably just more gifts being delivered.
很快回来
I'll be right back.
-你好  -你好  艾伦先生
- Hello? - Hello, Mr. Allen.
多米尼克
Dominic?
你的察觉能力和智力真的很敏锐
You really have an acute sense of detection. And wit.
但如我所说  艾伦先生
But like I said, Mr. Allen.
你察觉不到我的计谋有多万无一失
You are incapable of seeing the breadth of my machinations.
迪沃
DeVoe?
你真该认真听老师讲课
You really should have listened to your teacher.
怎么可能
How is this possible?
我说了我有个很重要的买家  小多
I told you I have a very important buyer, Dom.
跟说好的一样
As promised.
跟另一个精明的女人做生意总是很有趣
Always a pleasure doing business with another savvy woman.
求你  别这么对我
Please, don't do this to me.
我不会对你做什么
I won't be doing anything to you.
幸会  多米尼克·兰斯
Pleased to meet you, Dominic Lance.
或者该叫你六号目标
Or should I say Subject Six?
我创造了很多超能力者
I have created many meta humans,
但只有你的特殊超能力能让我
but only your unique abilities allow me to do...
这样做
this.
艾伦先生  三个月前
You see, Mr. Allen, three months ago
你从神速力中焕然新生
you emerged from the Speed Force a new man.
为了让你和世人见识到我的计划
And in order for you and the world to experience my plan,
我也需要重生
I, too, needed to be reborn.
如果你伤害我的家人
If you hurt my family...
我对你的家人没兴趣
I have no interest in your family.
而且等你消失后总得有人
Besides, you're gonna need someone to miss you
思念你
when you're gone.
你做了什么
What did you do?
我只是给你留了一样东西
I merely left something for you.
可以说是转赠的礼物
It's a re-gift, as it were.
我不再需要它了
I don't have need for it anymore.
艾伦
Allen?
中城警局  开门
CCPD. Open up.
快开门
Open up in there.
破门  破门  破门
Breach, breach, breach.
别跑
Don't run.
上上上
Move, move, move, move, move!
把手放到看得见的地方  巴里
Keep your hands where I can see them, Barry.
安全
Clear!
Clear.
巴里·艾伦  你因谋杀
Barry Allen, you're under arrest
克利福德·迪沃被捕了
for the murder of Clifford DeVoe.
抱歉  我得走了
Excuse me. I have to go.
但是非常感谢
But thank you so much.
当然  谢谢你过来
Of course. Thank you for coming.
-大家圣诞节快乐  -圣诞快乐
- Merry Christmas to you all. - Merry Christmas.
我说了会陪在你身边
Told you I will stand beside you.
始终如此
Always.
现在去开启大悟之道吧
Now let's bring about the enlightment.